Guide to the Yale University Library Gift Acknowledgments
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library gift acknowledgments
1920-2005
RU 203
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
72.5
The records consist of copies of acknowledgments sent to donors by the Acquisitions Department for gifts received by the Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-C (YRG 32-C), Records of Yale University Library departments and offices.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted to the office of origin only.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of copies of acknowledgments sent to donors by the Acquisitions Department for gifts received by the Yale University Library.
Academic libraries -- Acquisitions; Libraries -- Gifts, legacies; Technical services (Libraries); Yale University. Library
- Gift acknowledgements, circa 1979-1980; Accession 1981-A-057
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted to office of origin only.
  - A -B, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - C - L, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - M - T, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - U - Z, statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
- Donor cards, circa 1920-1978; Accession 1982-A-057
  - A-Andrew (Box 1)
  - Andrews-Barnes (Box 2)
  - Barnett-Blair (Box 3)
  - Blais-Brown (Box 4)
  - Brownback-Celanese (Box 5)
  - Celeste-Coll (Box 6)
  - Collacott-Currier (Box 7)
  - Curro-Dodge (Box 8)
  - Dodson-Everglades (Box 9)
  - Everhart-Friedman (Box 10)
  - Friedrich-Goodwin (Box 11)
  - Goodyear-Harter (Box 12)
  - Hartford-Hollander (Box 13)
  - Hollcroft-Investors (Box 14)
  - Ioannou-Kaylor (Box 15)
  - Kaynor-Lambert (Box 16)
  - Lambin-Lockmiller (Box 17)
  - Lockwood-Marinates (Box 18)
  - Marine-Monapert (Box 19)
  - Montclair -Nevitre? (Box 20)
  - New -Oz (Box 21)
  - P-Portell (Box 22)
  - Porter-Rizir (Box 23)
  - Roache - Schenck (Box 24)
  - Schenker - Smyth (Box 25)
  - Snead - Surasky (Box 26)
  - Surface - Trumpener (Box 27)
  - Trumper - Vicente (Box 28)
  - Vickerman - Whitehill (Box 29)
  - Whitehouse - Yomiuv (Box 30)
  - Yonkers - Z (Box 31)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1980-1981; Accession 1982-A-058
  - A-E, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - F-K, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - L-Q, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - R-W, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  - Ex-statistics, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1981-1982; Accession 1983-A-106
  - A - E, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - F - L, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - M - Sz, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - T - Z, statistics, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1982-1983; Accession 1984-A-070
  - A-D, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 6)
  - E-I, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7 - 12)
  - J-O, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13 - 19)
  - P-S, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 20 - 24)
  - T-Z, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 25 - 29)
  - Yale, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Appraisals over $1000, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Gifts received records, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1983-1984; Accession 1985-A-062
  - A - E, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - F - K, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - L - R, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - S - Wh, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Wi - Z, statistics, daily sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1984-1985; Accession 1986-A-100
  - A -F, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - G - L, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - M - R, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - S -T, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - U - Z, report sheets, statistics, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
- Gift acknowledgements and donor cards, 1973-1986; Accession 1988-A-004
  - Acknowledgments, 1985-1986
    - A - B (Box 11)
    - C-G (Box 12)
    - H - K (Box 13)
    - L-Q (Box 14)
    - R - V (Box 15)
    - W-Statistics (Box 16)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1986-1987; Accession 1988-A-101
  - A - E, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - F - L, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - M -S, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - T - Z, daily entry sheets, statistics, annual report, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1987-1988; Accession 1989-A-010
  - A - E, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - F - K (Box 2)
  - L - O, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - P - Si, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Sm - Z, daily reports, 1987-1988 (Box 5)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1988-1989; Accession 1990-A-003
  - A -G, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - H - M, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - N - S, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - T -Z, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
- Gift acknowledgements, circa 1989-1990; Accession 1991-A-005
  - A -G, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - H - M, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - N -T, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - U - Z, Yale departments and divisions, daily records, appraisals over $1000, annual report, statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1990-1992; Accession 1993-A-018
  - Gift acknowledgments
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 10)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11 - 20)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1991-1993; Accession 1994-A-006
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 29)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1993-1994; Accession 1995-A-001
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1993-1994
    - A - O (Box 1, Folder 1 - 19)
    - P -Z (Box 2, Folder 20 - 29)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1991-1997; Accession 1998-A-031
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1991-1997 (Box 1)
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1991-1997 (Box 2)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1997-1998; Accession 1999-A-007
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1998-1999; Accession 2000-A-041
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
- Gift acknowledgements, 1999-2000; Accession 2001-A-009
  - Gift acknowledgments, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
- Gift acknowledgements, 2000-2002; Accession 2003-A-013
  - Gift acknowledgments, 2000-2002 (Box 1)
- Gift acknowledgements, 2002-2003; Accession 2004-A-128
  - Gift acknowledgments, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
- Gift acknowledgements, 2003-2004; Accession 2008-A-040
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged alphabetically by name
  - Gift acknowledgments, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
- Gift acknowledgements, 2004-2005; Accession 2008-A-045
  - Gift acknowledgments, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
- Gift acknowledgements, 2005-2007; Accession 2008-A-090
  - 2005 Jul - 2006 Jun
    - A-K (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - L-R (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - S-Z (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2006 Jul - 2007 Jun
    - A-I (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - J-O (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - P-Z (Box 1, Folder 6)